Curriculum Vitae

Full Name: Saman Sadiq Redha Jawher

Date of Birth: January 1990

Current Address: Naz City, Gulan Str, Erbil, Iraq

Nationality: Iraqi – Kurdish

Marital Status: Single

Mobile Number: +9647508183778

Email Address: saman.sadiq.redha@gmail.com

BIO:

An ambitious, smart, and talented with ten years of private sector experiences. Able to balance multiple tasks, having worked for years in a multitude of jobs with amble experience in administration, researching, reports, and record keeping. A detail oriented, independent, and punctual. Aiming to take new challenges.

Education:

2010 - 2014

Cihan University, Erbil, Iraq

Degree and Major: Bachelor Degree in Computer Science

LANGUAGES:

1. Kurdish (Mother language) (Excellent: Reading, writing, and speaking).

2. English (Very Good: Reading, writing, and speaking).

3. Arabic (Excellent: Reading, writing, and speaking).

Computer skills:

Microsoft Office package

Word (Very Good)

Excel (Good)

Power Point (Very Good)

Experience:

1- Employer: SAS Automotive Services Company, LTD

Position: Office Manager

Location: 100 Meter, Erbil, Iraq

Date: Jul, 2020 - Present

Work Specifications:

• Perform accurate research and analysis.

• Compile, proofread and revise drafts of documents and reports.

- Prepare reports, presentations and correspondence accurately and swiftly.
- Coordinate arrangements, meetings, and conferences as assigned.
- Daily record keeping and filing of documents.
- Professionally greet and receive guests and clients.
- Ensure efficient and effective administrative information and assistance.



2- Employer: Human Appeal Organization Position: Admin & Finance Assistant Location: Dream City, Erbil, Iraq

Date: Oct, 2019- Feb, 2020

Work Specifications:

- Assisting in dealing with Government Offices, Ministries related to HA projects.
- Maintenance follow up for office building and Guest houses.
- Itinerary management.
- Assist in arranging meetings and events.
- Procurement and finance duties.
- Supervise the cleaners in the office and guesthouses.
- Follow up the monthly office supplies.
- Follow up the pre-employment requirements and make sure that all of the documents are submitted.
- **3-** Employer: Mass Global Energy

Position: Administrator

Location: Perdawood, Makhmour road, Erbil, Iraq

Date: Jan, 2015 - Sep, 2019

Work Specifications:

- Making sure that the company's policies are being complied by all of the employees.
- Attendance and Leave management for more than 250 staff members.
- Issuing residence permits and visas.
- Translating and drafting the official letters and reports (English Arabic).
- Itinerary management.
- Arranging and taking notes of meetings.
- Arranging and evaluating the interviews.
- Documentation and archiving.
- Logistics and procurement.

4- Employer: Carrier Company

Position: Spare Parts Controller Location: Koya Street, Erbil, Iraq

Date: Jan, 2011- Dec, 2014

Work Specifications:

- Responsible on day to day parts supply.
- Prepare and process dispatch paperwork including progress sheets, picking lists, and delivery notes.
- Update internal and external customers on progress of parts supply.
- Finalize sales invoices to be processed by the Finance Team.
- Encourage business retention through proactive phone and email correspondence.
- Manage and develop maintenance reports.

References:

Available upon request.